Guide to the Michael G. Shively papers,1976-1995.
Shively, Michael G. papers,1976-1995
- Series III. Chronological Files/Correspondence
  - Correspondence 90, 5/99 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 91, 6/99 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence 92, 7/99-8/99 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 93, 8/99-9/99 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence 94, 9/99-10/99 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence 95, 10/99-11/99 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence 96, 11/99 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence 97, 11/99-12/99 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence 98, 12/99 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence 99, 12/99-1/00 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence 100, 1/00-2/00 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence 101, 2/00-3/00 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence 102, 3/00-4/00 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence 103, 5/00 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence 104, 6/00-7/00 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence 122, 2001-11-2001-12 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence 123, 2001-12-2002-01 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 124, 2002-01-2002-02 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence 125, 2002-02-2002-03 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 126, 2002-03-2002-04 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence 127, 2002-04-2002-05 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence 128, 2002-05-2002-07 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence 129, 2002-07-2002-08 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence 130, 2002-08-2002-09 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence 131, 2002-09-2002-10 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence 132, 2002-11 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence 133, 2002-11-2002-12 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence 134, 2003-01 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence 135, 2003-01-2003-02 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence 136, 2003-02-2003-03 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence 137, 2003-03-2003-04 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence 138, 2003-04 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence 139, 2003-04-2003-05 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 140, 2003-05-2003-06 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence 141, 2003-06-2003-07 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 142, 2003-07-2003-08 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence 143, 2003-08-2003-09 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence 144, 2003-09-2003-10 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence 145, 2003-10-2003-11 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence 146, 2003-11-2003-12 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence 147, 2003-12-2004-01 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence 148, 2004-01-2004-02 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence 149, 2004-02-2004-03 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence 150, 2004-03-2004-04 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Maya Philipson's Senior Thesis (Antioch College), 2003 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence 151, April-June 2004 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
  - Correspondence 152, March-July 2004 (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence 153, July-September 2004 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
  - Correspondence 154, September-November 2004 (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
  - Correspondence 155, November-December 2004 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence 156, December 2004-January 2005 (Box 21, Folder 11-12)
  - Correspondence 157, January-February 2005 (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
  - Pat Califia Correspondence, 8/83-9/86 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #1, 1982-83 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #2, 1983-88 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #3, 1990-91 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #4, 1990-91 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #5, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #6, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #7, 1991-92 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #8, 1991-92 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #9, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #10, 1991-93 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #11, 1993-94 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Classified Ad Correspondence #12, 1994-95 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Paul Moor Correspondence, 7/99-5/00 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - David Cederwall Correspondence, 7/84-11/88 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Davey Stewart File (Died of AIDS), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Boy with Arms Akimbo Materials (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - LPI Budget Information (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous LPI Materials (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Series IV. Damron
  - Damron Promotional Materials #1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Damron Promotional Materials #2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Damron Promotional Materials #3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Damron Promotional Materials #4 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Damron Promotional Materials #5 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Damron financial files, July 1999-May 2001 (Box 18)
  - Damron financial files, June 2001-Dec. 2002 (Box 19)
  - Damron Co. files, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Damron Co. files, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 2-3)
  - Damron. Co, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 4-6)
  - Damron Co. files, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
  - Damron Co. files, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
  - Damron Co. files, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
  - Damron Co. files, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
  - Damron Co. files: Web User Emails, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Damron Co. files: Inter-office Emails, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
  - Delbex Estate, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 18-19)
  - Delbex Estate, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Last will and testament of Dan Delbex, creating the Delbex/Damron Trust, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2001-03 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2001-05-2002-08 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2002-09-2003-01 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2003-01-2003-03 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2003-04 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2003-05-2003-06 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2003-06-2003-08 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2003-09 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2003-11-2003-12 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2004-01-2004-02 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2004-03-2004-08 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, 2004-09-2004-10 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Sample web administrator letters - user questions, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, September 2004 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, October 2004 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, November 2004 (Box 21, Folder 17-18)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, December 2004 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, January 2005 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Damron Staff and Subscriber Correspondence, February 2005 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Damron Staff and Boards of Directors Meeting Materials, March 2002 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Damron Staff and Boards of Directors Meeting Materials, September 2003 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Damron Staff and Boards of Directors Meeting Materials, October 2003 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Damron Staff and Boards of Directors Meeting Materials, November-December 2003 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Damron Staff and Boards of Directors Meeting Materials, January 2004 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Damron Staff and Boards of Directors Meeting Materials, February 2004 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Damron Staff and Boards of Directors Meeting Materials, March 2004 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Damron Staff and Boards of Directors Meeting Materials, April 2004 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Damron Staff and Boards of Directors Meeting Materials, May 2004 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Damron Staff and Boards of Directors Meeting Materials, June 2004 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Damron Staff and Boards of Directors Meeting Materials, July-August 2004 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - North Bay Area,CA - Gay Men's Organizations, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - North Bay Area,CA - Gay Men's Organizations, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - North Bay Area,CA - Gay Men's Organizations, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Interview with Gina Gatta, President of Damron Company in OutTraveler, January-February 2005 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Admin files, 2000-04-2000-12 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Admin files, 2000-07-2000-08 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Admin files, 2001-03-2001-08 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Admin files, 2001-05-2001-09 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Admin files, 2001-12-2002-03 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Admin files, 2002-04-2002-09 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Admin files, 2003-01-2003-06 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Admin files, 2003-06-2003-12 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Damron Co. files, 1997-01-1997-04 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Damron Co. files, 1997-05-1997-09 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Damron Co. files, 1997-10-1997-12 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Damron Co. files, 1998-01-1998-04 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Damron Co. files, 1998-04-1998-07 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Damron Co. files, 1998-08-1998-11 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Damron Co. files, 1998-11-1998-12 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Damron Co. files, 1998-12-1999-04 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Damron Co. files, 1999-03-1999-09 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Damron Co. files, 1999-09-1999-12 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - VeriSign documents, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Advertising items, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-01 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-02 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-03 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-04 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-05 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-06 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-07 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-08 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-09 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-10 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-11 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2003-12 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-01 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-02 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-03 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-04 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-05 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-06 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-07 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-08 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-09 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-10 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-11 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Damron online monthly business activity reports, 2004-12 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Series V. Ephemera
  - Gay Games IV hat with buttons, 1994; MU-2502 (Box 28)
  - Damron pocket knife, 2004; MU-2503 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - The Dick Tie neck tie, 1988; MU-2504; B and B Marketing (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Promotional item sent to Damron mail order for possible sale
  - Bulk Male Screen Shots Volume One, 1999; CD-4787; AfterImage Studios, Inc. (Box 27)
  - Valois Travel, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - OurTribe Marketing, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Meat Market Gay Erotic Cardpack, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Advertising, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Ephemera, Undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Love Heals All Wounds: Characters With Disabilities in Romance Novels, 2003; Philipson, Maya (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Senior thesis
  - The Singing Rage, 1986; SR-31457; Rage, Christopher; Wild Twin Production; 12" vinyl (Box 21)
    Signed by the artist, numbered 203/1000 | CR1001